[
    {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "1 + 1 = ?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "b",
            "list": {
                "a": "1",
                "b": "2",
                "c": "3",
                "d": "4"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "77 + 33 = ?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "c",
            "list": {
                "a": "99",
                "b": "100",
                "c": "110",
                "d": "120"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "25 * 25 = ?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "c",
            "list": {
                "a": "225",
                "b": "455",
                "c": "625",
                "d": "2525"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "6 / (2 * (1 + 2)) = ?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "b",
            "list": {
                "a": "0",
                "b": "1",
                "c": "3",
                "d": "9"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "(6 / 2) * (1 + 2) = ?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "d",
            "list": {
                "a": "0",
                "b": "1",
                "c": "3",
                "d": "9"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "Math.sqrt(36) = ?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "b",
            "list": {
                "a": "-6, 6",
                "b": "6",
                "c": "-36, 36",
                "d": "36"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "Math.pow(8, 2) = ?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "d",
            "list": {
                "a": "2",
                "b": "8",
                "c": "16",
                "d": "64"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "Math.pow(7, -2) = ?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "c",
            "list": {
                "a": "49",
                "b": "-49",
                "c": "1/49",
                "d": "-1/49"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "Math.pow(9, 0.5) = ?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "a",
            "list": {
                "a": "3",
                "b": "4.5",
                "c": "9",
                "d": "45"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "Find x: x^2 - 4 = 0",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "c",
            "list": {
                "a": "2",
                "b": "-2",
                "c": "-2, 2",
                "d": "4"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "When did the war of 1812 started?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "b",
            "list": {
                "a": "1810",
                "b": "1812",
                "c": "1815",
                "d": "1818"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "When did the war of 1812 ended?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "c",
            "list": {
                "a": "1810",
                "b": "1812",
                "c": "1815",
                "d": "1818"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "Who is the first person in space?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "a",
            "list": {
                "a": "Yuri Gagarin",
                "b": "Alan Shepard",
                "c": "Neil Armstrong",
                "d": "Pavel Popovich"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "Who is the first woman in space?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "c",
            "list": {
                "a": "Svetlana Savitskaya",
                "b": "Sally Ride",
                "c": "Valentina Tereshkova",
                "d": "Christa McAuliffe"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "Who is the first Asian in space?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "d",
            "list": {
                "a": "Taylor Wang",
                "b": "Jügderdemidiin Gürragchaa",
                "c": "Rakesh Sharma",
                "d": "Phạm Tuân"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "Which event did not occer during \"Pax Britannica\" period?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "a",
            "list": {
                "a": "French revolution",
                "b": "Opium wars",
                "c": "Ireland's Great Famine",
                "d": "Industrial revolution"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "Which monarch is not related to others?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "b",
            "list": {
                "a": "George V",
                "b": "Franz Joseph I",
                "c": "Nicholas II",
                "d": "Wilhelm II"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "When did Austria Empire changed to Austro-Hungarian Empire?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "b",
            "list": {
                "a": "1848",
                "b": "1867",
                "c": "1871",
                "d": "1914"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "When did the US announce the end of involvement in Vietnam?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "c",
            "list": {
                "a": "1969",
                "b": "1971",
                "c": "1973",
                "d": "1975"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "Who is the most \"Seiso\" member in Hololive?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "b",
            "list": {
                "a": "Hoshimachi Suisei",
                "b": "Tokino Sora",
                "c": "Honshou Marine",
                "d": "Sakura Miko"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "21",
        "question": "Who is called \"Mama\" in Hololive?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "c",
            "list": {
                "a": "Tokino Sora",
                "b": "Nekomata Okayu",
                "c": "Ookami Mio",
                "d": "Shirakami Fubuki"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "22",
        "question": "Which space mission was the first that landed on the Moon?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "c",
            "list": {
                "a": "Sputnik 1",
                "b": "Vostok 1",
                "c": "Apollo 11",
                "d": "Apollo 13"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "23",
        "question": "Which space mission was the first that carried an astronaut/cosmonaut to the space?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "b",
            "list": {
                "a": "Sputnik 1",
                "b": "Vostok 1",
                "c": "Apollo 11",
                "d": "Apollo 13"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "24",
        "question": "Which one was the first satellite launched to the space?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "a",
            "list": {
                "a": "Sputnik 1",
                "b": "Vostok 1",
                "c": "Apollo 11",
                "d": "Apollo 13"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "25",
        "question": "Which space mission experienced accident and caused the crews to return to the Earth?",
        "choices": {
            "answer": "d",
            "list": {
                "a": "Sputnik 1",
                "b": "Vostok 1",
                "c": "Apollo 11",
                "d": "Apollo 13"
            }
        }
    }
]